pokerpages.com 2003-12-07

# Poker Pages - Poker Articles, Tournaments, & Directory

| 

**Privacy Policy**

PokerPages is committed to respecting your choices regarding privacy. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you register for any tournament, are on the PokerPages web site, and when you use any PokerPages' products or services. This policy also covers treatment of any personally identifiable information that our business partners share with us or that we may collect on a partner's site. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

  * PokerPages collects personally identifiable information when you register for a PokerPages account, when you use certain PokerPages products or services, and when you visit PokerPages web pages. We may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with PokerPages we ask for information including but not limited to: your name, email address, birth date, gender, street address, zip code, photoID type and number, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with PokerPages and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * PokerPages also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, PokerPages cookie information and the page you requested. 
  * PokerPages uses information for several general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to customize the advertising and service content you see, for feedback regarding PokerPages and PokerPages' partners, and to contact you about specials and new products to which you've indicated interest. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * PokerPages will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 
  * PokerPages may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of PokerPages to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the PokerPages Terms of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Cookies**

  * PokerPages may set and access PokerPages cookies on your computer. 
  * PokerPages allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to PokerPages' cookies. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

  * PokerPages gives you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time, by contacting us with your desired changes. You can change nearly all your account information except your Username (see delete account below to change your username). Please be sure to include your Username & present Password, and your first and last name in the email for identification purposes. 
  * You may request deletion of your entire PokerPages account by contacting us with your desired to cancel the account. In your email to us, please be sure to include your Username & present Password, and your first and last name in the email for identification purposes. You will be emailed asking to confirm that you want your account deleted. When you reply to this email, your account will be deleted, so allow 3-5 business days for these emails to go back and forth when planning to delete your account. If you are a PokerSchool Online customer, see Terms of Service for how billing is tied to canceling your account. 

**Security**

  * Your Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * PokerPages may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. Your continued usage of PokerPages Services constitutes agreement to this Policy and to any changes to it. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

  * We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or suggestions, please email [support@pokerpages.com](mailto:support@pokerpages.com). 

| |    
 [**Paradise Poker  
World's Largest   
Online Poker Room** ](http://www.pokerpages.com/adserver/click.php?bannerID=263&cachebuster=767949507)

[](http://www.pokerpages.com/adserver/click.php?bannerID=705&cachebuster=780840471)[**BugsysClub  
3 X $10,000   
WSOP SEATS**](http://www.bugsysclub.com/club/poker/wsop-2004.htm)

[PartyPoker.com  
25,000+ Players  
$100 EXTRA](http://www.pokerpages.com/adserver/click.php?bannerID=850&cachebuster=676764018)

[**BadBeat $6,079  
$1,000 added daily   
Planet Poker **](http://www.pokerpages.com/adserver/click.php?bannerID=902&cachebuster=552236528)

[Play Poker  
No Downloads  
PokerRoom.com](http://www.pokerpages.com/adserver/click.php?bannerID=725&cachebuster=68326673)

[Multiplayer   
Poker at   
Ladbrokespoker](http://www.pokerpages.com/adserver/click.php?bannerID=875&cachebuster=612373996)

[$3 Million  
WSOP Shootout  
TruePoker.com](http://www.pokerpages.com/adserver/click.php?bannerID=718&cachebuster=662974970)

|
